I'm going to push and push and push and push and push.
If I win a little, I'll get my wish.
Wow!
Yay!
I feel like that!
Guess Sumo, clearly!
I'm in!
Go, go, go!
Are you guys gonna do Push Sumo together?
Oh!
Go for it!
He's looking me right in the eye.
Do you like my hair?
Slow it down!
Come on!
Come on! Come on!
Pushing sumo!
No!
Aah!
Aaah!
Oh, man! I'm gonna extend it!
Hey!
I got Aki-chan!
Yay!
Please!
Is it okay?
Are you sure you want to do this show?
Why are you saying that?why are you saying that?
CAR
I won't let you boo boo.
Is
Is me
What do you want to do with Aki-chan this time?
I want to end with a little push-wrestling.
What are you gonna do?
Why push wrestling?
It's weird. Why are you pushing too much?
I'm just saying, you know, push, push, push, push...
I mean, push and push.
That's right.
I'm looking forward to rewarding you when I win.
Okay? The reward is...
Anything you push.
Cute.
Can I get your address?
No, no, no.
Eat.
Go ahead.
Hey!
Push-pull sumo!
Nogi-na-na-na-na!
First time I learned it.
I'm sorry.
I'm...
Cute!
Anagi, of course.Anagi, of course.
Oh, you're disqualified.
You're disqualified.
I won't answer it again
Cute.
I could pull it out from the push.
I could pull it out.
Oh!
Oh, it's recycled.
I can pull it out.
Touch.
There he is.
Just a second.
I've been pushing that thing around your waist.
I still need it.
I need it now.
Announcement.
I'm up.
Ahhh
Ahhh...
So cute!
Win!
What kind of request are you going to make, Hana-chan?
Well, let's see... I've put away the link that says I like you, Hana-chan.
Is that okay?
I like you, Hana-chan.
Wow!Oh, my God!
I'm hit!
You got me!
You're so cute!
I'm hit!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Can I get a heart massage, please?
I'm sorry to disturb you like this.
So I've brought all of you from Iginari Talk.
Mr. Iginari, right?
The youngest!
Weak-looking...
You're making fun of us.
I'm making fun of them.
So my choice for the showdown is...
Hinamon!
Go for it!
Hey!
Yes, sir.
You're still here!
You're good.
Strong.
Strong, strong, strong.
Good luck.
Killer. Strong.
Real strong.
Not to be outdone.
Come on.Come on.
Strong. Strong.
Support me.
Back me up.
I knew you were taking him with you.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go! Let's go!
Come on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Thank you.
I knew I could win with this guy.
Yuzu.
We've been licked.
Yeah, you did.
You're a real champ, huh? Yeah, he's got me beat.
Ta-da!
You won them all?
They both look so strong.
If Kaya wins, I'll buy you a barbecue.
Idiot!
If Yuzu wins...
I'll stay at a fancy hotel.
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no...
Hey, hey, hey!
Yes, kyoyo yay!
I'm staying!Remaining!
Pantomile.
You're the one who got in.
That guy's kind of a pain in the ass.
He's a pain in the ass.
Oh, he looks so strong.
He seems strong.
He looks strong!
I have to go to the carpenters' table.
Oh, Mera's carpenter!
I have to sit in the carpenter's chair
I have to sit in the carpenter's chair.
You're a carpenter!
That's great!
Oh, that's good!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Ready?
Let's go!
Let's do it.
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Go, go, go, go
Se-no!
Se-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no
Let's do it!
Let's go!
Quickly!
with one power
100%.
One power.All in one power
100% by
100% by 100%.
At the end.
I did it.
No more.
It's a draw.
Draw.
Who wants to do it?
Then...
Prince of Whimsy
Prince of Whim
The reason why?
Because he looks weak.
LOL
The last one
BGM
Table Tennis Yoyoi Robotter
LOL!
Oh, it feels too good.
Oh, ah, it's too close.
Ah, ah, it's too close.
It's not a compliment.
Oh, oh, it's so close.
Let's hear it in your voice. Let's hear it in your voice.Let's hear it in your voice. Let's hear it in your voice.
No more, no more, no more, no more, no more, no more, no more, no more, no more, no more, no more.
It's over, it's over
Flowers lose
Akushushi
Lost to flowers
Oh, no, no, no!
It's a red card.
Red card.
I'm sorry.
He's here.
Our oldest is here.
That's funny.
It's okay.
The oldest.
Oldest
Moeka Sasaki wants to be friends with Lucky, but she can't seem to get along with him at all.
Cute!
Please leave Karap out!
Carap.
Why? Why?
I don't know, I don't care, but it's okay.
Hey!
Yes, I'm in the moodYes. Spirits.
Good.
Wow.
That was good.
More.
Wow.
Keekettins.
Ah.
Lucky's seriously.
Sort of.
Yes. So...
The keyboard behind Talking Thing.
I'm done.
Ooh.
Ooh!
The candyflash was a draw.
They're buddies!
You mean they're good friends, right?
No, but I'm taking it easy on Uzilla.
What? Whoozilla's holding back?
She's still going all out.
Whale, too?
Whale too?
Whale too?And the whale?
Hey.
Ahhh...
Aaaaah!
Yes, that's right!
Our senior, Yuri-chan Tamaishi of Z-san came to our club!
Yay!
Congratulations!
Oh my gosh!
I know you're busy, so I'll just take a quick look.
You're busy.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
It's almost time for the first shift.
I'm a little nervous.
Slightly, slightly...
Subtle.
Soberly
I'm pushing it!
There is Mr. Suzuki.
To be told that I'm pushing him every time.
Oh, I see.
Maybe that's the kind of reaction you're getting.
It's all good.
I love what you're doing.
I'm glad.
Push Sumo
Pushing sumo.
Push Sumo?
Yes, it's good.
If Mayaka wins.If Mayaka wins, yes.
Yes, okay.
There are cases where the inside wins.
But this is pretty...
Seriously.
I'm serious.
I'm serious
Absolutely, but I'm serious.
All right.
Here we go.
Yes!
Yes!Yes, sir.
I'm being nice, aren't I?
I'm so nice to you.
I showed my gentleness.
You lost, didn't you?
Until tomorrow.
I'm so happy.
Well, Moeka, I have a favor to ask.
I was going to ask for your contact information.
Uh, can you hold my phone for a second?
Oh, that kind of thing.
Actually, he has a cell phone.
Oh, I have to smack Annie because she's in the Annie's Army.
Oh, no.
Okay, sure.
Sure, sure.
Of course, of course, of course.
I'm so happy.
Now we're really going to celebrate.
Really?
But, you know, I'm pretty early, too, Chi-chan. Birthday.
That's right.
Ippo is number one every year.
Our image of you is more like Mo-chan's,
I think she might want it a little more.
No, from now on.
Don't lose. Don't lose.
Yes, I won't lose.
Disgusting.
Grazy.
Well, you'll have to hear it from Annie.
Sorry, sober.
I'm sorry, Mr. Hamaguchi's session.
Member's session.
Come here.
You can tighten up.
I never sent you a message.
Thank you.
Come to Annie.
You stopped being a photographer?
I did.
I'm about to.
I'm sorry about earlier.
I had the members bring him back.
Oh, that's right.
But can I ask you to change the stage?
Sure.
This one too.
Yuzuki-chan here, too.
You.
Can I do it?
Can you do it to me? Can I do it?
Can you do it to me?
On our end.
You can do yours.
Who did you do it to, you guys?
The senior member of our group came to see us.
Yay.
I thought you were a diginato.
Wow.
Did I say that?
Congratulations.